Adam Huszka

7/7 The Avenue, Windsor 3181, VIC (04)-2140-3638 adamhuszka@gmail.com www.adamhuszka.com Facebook page



Goal:

To get a position as a photographer and to gain further experience in this field by taking up challenging and interesting photography project assignments. I have been involved in various assignments of photography - portraying social issues, architecture photography as well as fashion and beauty photography.

Education:

- Bachelors Degree in IT at Berzsenyi Daniel College (BDF), Hungary
- Graduated as Applied Photographer in 2009 at Stalter Photography Academy, Hungary

Professional Experience:

2003 - 2004: IT Supervisor / Citroën Szombathely/

2006 - 2007: DTP operator /Tericum Book Publisher, Budapest/
Performing complex duties, including book cover creation (Illustrator, Photoshop),
photo manipulation (Photoshop), text wrapping (InDesign) and advertisement
creation (Flash).

2007 - 2009: Technical Illustrator /Sigma Kudos Hungary Ltd., Budapest/
 2009 - 2011: Technical Illustrator /SDI Global Solutions Hungary Ltd., Budapest/

2006 - : Freelance Photographer

Undertook various types of photography assignments:

- creating photos of buildings exteriors and interiors (e.g. Budapest Airport)
- shooting model portfolios in studio (with 2 light sources) and outdoors
- depicting social issues by creating photo essays
- handling graphical requirements for business clients creating brochures and corporate presentations, DTP projects and book covers
- post-processing, retouching and manipulating in Adobe Photoshop CS5
- photographing events and concerts as the official photographer
- covering a few weddings

Communication and Interpersonal Skills:

- Taking full responsibility for my work
- Being reliable and punctual
- I always have a positive attitude and a willingness to learn

Computer Skills:

Windows systems

Applications - Adobe Creative Suite 5 (Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator), Lightroom 3,

Additional Skills:

6x6 and 35mm cameras, black&white film processing and printing

Exhibits and publications:

- Photographer's Forum Best of 2011 Photography Book
- Student Works Exhibition Kópia Exhibition Room, Budapest
- Children of the World Exhibition (1 photograph along with the Hungarian National Collection)
- FotoBlur Magazine(UK) Issue 7 and 8
- Bulb Magazine(Cr) Issue 12
- Digital Camera Magazine(UK) Hot shots section, Issue 108
- 168 Óra report photos about social issues
- Published book covers

References:

Portfolio site - <u>www.adamhuszka.com</u> Other references available on request







